Guide to the Bryant Fleming plans, [ca. 1904-1937]
Fleming, Bryant plans
- Series II. Clients J-P
  - Nelson, C. L. Location: Louisville, Kentucky
    - Front elevation of Residence, by Architects N. M. Woods "void" penciled on print, 1912 (Box 12)
      Sheet # 221
    - Rear elevation of Residence, by Architects N. M. Woods "void" penciled on print, 1912 (Box 12)
      Sheet # 222
    - Roof Plan, by Architects N. M. Woods "void" penciled on print, 1912 (Box 12)
      Sheet # 223
    - Sketch of Rear Garden, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
      Sheet # 224
    - First floor Plan, by Architects N. M. Woods "void" penciled on print, Undated (Box 12)
      Sheet # 225
    - Second floor Plan, by Architects N. M. Woods "void" penciled on print, 1912 (Box 12)
      Sheet # 226
    - Basement Plan, by Architects N. M. Woods "void" penciled on print, 1912 (Box 12)
      Sheet # 227
    - Topographical plan (McDonald & Dodd, Architects), 1911 (Box 12)
      Sheet # 228
    - Topographical plan (McDonald & Dodd, Architects), 1911 (Box 12)
      Sheet # 229
  - Paine, Nathan Location: Oshkosh, Wisconsin
    - Details of Boudoir, 1930 (Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1
      Format: Sepia
    - Guest room, 1929 (Box 2)
      Sheet # 2
    - Laundry plan - room 5, 1929 (Folder 1)
      Sheet # 3
    - Suspended Canopy in Gallery, 1930 (Folder 1)
      Sheet # 4
    - Detail Panels Main Stair, 1930 (Folder 1)
      Sheet # 5
    - Full scale detail panel Main Stair 0/5, 1930 (Folder 1)
      Sheet # 6
    - Recreation room details, 1928 (Folder 1)
      Sheet # 7
    - Billiard room details, 1928 (Folder 2)
      Sheet # 8
    - Details of fireplace - Recreation room, 1930 (Folder 2)
      Sheet # 9
    - Recreation and Billiard rooms, 1928 (Folder 2)
      Sheet # 10
      Scale: 3/4"=1' and Full scale
    - Study for treatment of Dressing room, 1930 (Box 2)
      Sheet # 11
      Format: Sepia and colored pencil
    - 3" Scale detail of Library Room no.111, 1930 (Folder 2)
      Sheet # 12
      Scale: 3"=1' and Full scale
    - 3" Scale detail of Library Room 111, 1929 (Folder 2)
      Sheet # 13
    - Details of Recreation room, 1930 (Folder 3)
      Sheet # 14
    - Interior Elevations - Reception room, 1930 (Folder 3)
      Sheet # 15
    - Details of Reception room, 1929 (Folder 3)
      Sheet # 16
    - 3" scale details of Library room 111, 1930 (Folder 3)
      Sheet # 17
    - 3" scale details of Woodwork - North end of Living room, Undated (Folder 3)
      Sheet # 18
      Scale: 3"-1'
    - 3" scale details of Living room, 1929 (Folder 4)
      Sheet # 19
    - Wood ceiling in Living room, 1930 (Folder 4)
      Sheet # 20
    - Full scale detail of Tracery Panels - Living room, 1929 (Folder 4)
      Sheet # 21
      Scale: Full Scale
    - Details of north end of Living room, 1929 (Folder 4)
      Sheet # 22
    - Ceiling Beams - Stair Hall: First floor, 1929 (Box 2)
      Sheet # 23
    - Dining room details, 1930 (Folder 4)
      Sheet # 24
    - Dining room details, 1930 (Folder 5)
      Sheet # 25
    - Full scale Dining room details, 1929 (Folder 5)
      Sheet # 26
    - Guest room no. 208 - Elevations and details, 1928 (Box 2)
      Sheet # 27
      Scale: 1/2"=1' and Full scale
    - Guest room no. 210- Elevations and details, 1928 (Box 2)
      Sheet # 28
    - Owner bedroom no. 204- Elevations and plans, 1927 (Folder 5)
      Sheet # 29
    - General dimensional engineering layout, 1930 (Folder 5)
      Sheet # 30
      Format: Sepia, Oversized
    - Layout plan of Main Garden, 1930 (Folder 5)
      Sheet # 31
    - Vestibule and Dressing room no. 208, 1928 (Box 2)
      Sheet # 32
    - Revised study for landscape layout, 1926 (Box 2)
      Sheet # 33
      Format: Tracing paper and Crayon, Fair condition
    - Revised study for layout of house and property, 1925 (Box 2)
      Sheet # 34
      Format: Tracing paper and Crayon
    - Details of Boudoir, 1929 (Folder 6)
      Sheet # 35
    - Details of Boudoir, 1929 (Folder 6)
      Sheet # 36
    - Details of Boudoir, 1930 (Folder 6)
      Sheet # 37
    - South and East elevations / Main Garage, 1929 (Box 2)
      Sheet # 38
    - Second floor framing plan - Structural details / Main Garage, 1929 (Box 2)
      Sheet # 39
      Scale: 1/4"=1' and 1/2"=1'
    - North and West elevations / Main Garage, 1929 (Box 3)
      Sheet # 40
    - First floor framing plan and details / Main Garage, 1929 (Box 3)
      Sheet # 41
    - Window and Exterior door frame details / Main Garage, 1929 (Box 3)
      Sheet # 42
    - Second floor plan and Roof plan, 1929 (Box 3)
      Sheet # 43
    - Attic Framing plan and details / Main Garage, 1929 (Box 3)
      Sheet # 44
      Scale: 1/4"=1' and 3"=1'
    - Heating System diagram / Main Garage, 1929 (Box 3)
      Sheet # 45
    - Details of Interior door frames / Main Garage, 1929 (Box 3)
      Sheet # 46
    - Basement and First floor plans/ Main Garage, 1929 (Box 3)
      Sheet # 47
    - Basement and First floor plans/ Main Garage, 1929 (Box 3)
      Sheet # 48
    - Basement and First floor plans/ Main Garage, 1929 (Box 3)
      Sheet # 49
    - Full scale carving on plasters - Library, 1929 (Folder 6)
      Sheet # 50
    - Interior elevations and details - Dressing room no. 106, 1927 (Folder 6)
      Sheet # 51
      Condition:Poor - half of print has been torn off.
    - Basement and First floor plans/ Main Garage, 1929 (Box 4)
      Sheet # 52
    - Second floor and Roof plans/ Main Garage, 1929 (Box 4)
      Sheet # 53
    - South and East elevations / Main Garage, 1929 (Box 4)
      Sheet # 54
    - North and West elevations / Main Garage, 1929 (Box 4)
      Sheet # 55
    - First floor framing plan and details / Main Garage, 1929 (Box 4)
      Sheet # 56
    - Window and Exterior door frame details / Main Garage, 1929 (Box 4)
      Sheet # 57
    - Details of Interior door frames / Main Garage, 1929 (Box 4)
      Sheet # 58
    - Full scale sections of Garage doors and doors 101-108-1110-201-209, 1929 (Box 4)
      Sheet # 59
      Scale: Full Scale and 1/2"=1'
    - Elevations and details / Servant's Garage, 1928 (Box 4)
      Sheet # 60
    - Elevations and details / Servant's Garage, 1929 (Box 4)
      Sheet # 61
    - Details and elevations / Parking Garage, 1929 (Box 5)
      Sheet # 62
      Condition:
    - Flower sink in Breakfast room, 1929 (Folder 7)
      Sheet # 63
    - Full size details of Office and Room no.109, 1929 (Folder 7)
      Sheet # 64
      Scale: Full scale
    - 3" Scale detail of Office, 1929 (Folder 7)
      Sheet # 65
    - Details of cases in space over Dining Room, 1930 (Box 5)
      Sheet # 66
      Scale: 1/2"=1', 3"=1' and Full scale
    - Detail of Beamed Ceiling room 115, 1930 (Box 5)
      Sheet # 67
    - Sketch of Gallery, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 68
      Format: Sepia with pencil shading
    - Full scale details - Woodwork - Room 115, 1929 (Folder 7)
      Sheet # 69
      Scale: 3/4"=1' and full scale
    - Full scale details - Beamed ceiling - Motor Entrance, 1929 (Box 5)
      Sheet # 70
    - Elevations and Interiors - Motor Entrance, Undated (Folder 7)
      Sheet # 71
    - Detail of Gallery beams, 1930 (Box 5)
      Sheet # 72
    - Detail of cases in Service hall and Service corridor, 1930 (Box 5)
      Sheet # 73
    - Details and elevations of Bath room no. 1, 1929 (Box 5)
      Sheet # 74
      Scale: 1/2"=1' and 3"=1'
    - Bath 2 and Bath 3 - Plans, elevations and details, 1929 (Box 5)
      Sheet # 75
    - Dressing room 211 - Details and elevations, 1929 (Box 5)
      Sheet # 76
    - Vestibule and Dressing room no. 203 - Plan, elevations, 1928 (Box 5)
      Sheet # 77
    - Interior elevations - Dressing room no. 106, 1927 (Folder 8)
      Sheet # 78
    - Details of Fountain at Breakfast room, 1930 (Box 6)
      Sheet # 79
    - Foyer plan and elevations, Undated (Folder 8)
      Sheet # 80
    - Linen room no. 214 - Details and elevations, 1929 (Box 6)
      Sheet # 81
    - Maid's Bedroom no. 215 - Details and elevations, Undated (Box 6)
      Sheet # 82
    - Maid's Bedroom no. 171 - Details and plans, elevations, Undated (Box 6)
      Sheet # 83
    - Service hall no. 212, 1927 (Box 6)
      Sheet # 84
    - Bath room 4 and Dressing room 209, 1929 (Box 6)
      Sheet # 85
    - Interior elevations - Kitchen, Butler's pantry, Dining alcove, 1928 (Folder 8)
      8Sheet # 86
    - Wall tile layout - Kitchen, Butler's pantry, Dining alcove, 1930 (Folder 8)
      Sheet # 87
    - Service hall in basement - Caterer's room, Undated (Folder 8)
      Sheet # 88
    - Rail and Panel detail - Main stair, 1930 (Folder 9)
      Sheet # 99
    - Elevations: Upper Stair hall no. 206, Undated (Folder 9)
      Sheet # 100
    - Details of Upper stair hall room no. 206, 1929 (Folder 9)
      Sheet # 101
    - Full scale carving on Frieze - Library, 1929 (Folder 9)
      Sheet # 102
  - Client: Paul, Dr. W. K. Location: Belmont, New York
    - Arbor and lattice fence, by architects Esenwein & Johnson, Undated (Folder 21)
      Sheet # 380
    - Letter to Townsen and Fleming concerning gate hinges, 1906 (Box 9)
      Sheet # 381
      Format: Isaac Willets Estate" Stationery
    - Study sketch of pedestal for garden, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 414
    - Survey of Property, 1905 (Box 18)
      Sheet # 415
    - Details of arbor, by architects Esenwein & Johnson, Undated (Box 18)
      Sheet # 416
    - Full scale detail of stone work, 1909 (Folder 21)
      Sheet # 417
    - Elevations and plans of courtyard, by architects Esenwein & Johnson, Undated (Folder 21)
      Sheet # 418
    - Study of site arrangement, Undated (Folder 22)
      Sheet # 419
    - Full scale detail of upper hinge for office gate, Undated (Box 18)
      Sheet # 420
    - Sketch of garden plan, 1909 (Box 18)
      Sheet # 421
    - Notes on house and property, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 422
    - Rough sketch of site plan, Undated (Box 18)
      Sheet # 423
    - Sketches for gates, Undated (Box 18)
      Sheet # 424
    - Main entrance and smaller gates, 1906 (Box 18)
      Sheet # 425
    - Gates at drive entrance, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 426
    - Survey of Property, 1905 (Box 18)
      Sheet # 427
    - Plan and sections of reflecting pool, Undated (Box 18)
      Sheet # 428
    - Plan and sections of reflecting pool, 1905 (Box 18)
      Sheet # 429
    - Notes and figures on expenses, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 430
    - Notes and sketches of landscape work, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 431
    - Elevation of entrance gate, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 432
    - Garage plan, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 433
    - Plan for cottage, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 434
    - Garage elevation, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 435
    - Study of general site arrangement, Undated (Folder 22)
      Sheet # 436
    - Alterations to residence, by Architects Esenwein & Johnson, Undated (Folder 22)
      Sheet # 437
    - Plan of Site arrangement, 1905 (Folder 22)
      Sheet # 438
    - Wall separating property from street, 1906 (Folder 22)
      Sheet # 439
      Scale: 1/2"=1'; 1/20"=1'
    - Rough sketch of garden plan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 440
    - Rough sketch of garden plan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 441
    - Plan for site arrangement, 1905 (Folder 22)
      Sheet # 442
    - Rough sketch of garden plan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 443
    - Survey of Property, 1905 (Box 18)
      Sheet # 444
    - Elevation of main entrance gates, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 445
    - Sketches of reflecting pool, Undated (Box 18)
      Sheet # 446
    - Side elevation of Garage, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 447
    - Front elevation of Garage, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 448
    - Full scale details of Upper hinges, main entrance gates, Undated (Box 18)
      Sheet # 449
    - Detail of gate posts, Undated (Box 19)
      Sheet # 450
    - Rough survey of property, 1905 (Box 19)
      Sheet # 451
      Format: Gridded paper
    - Detail of gates, by Architects Esenwein & Johnson, Undated (Box 19)
      Sheet # 452
    - Full scale detail of Upper hinge, Long walk gate, Undated (Box 19)
      Sheet # 453
    - Full scale detail of Upper hinges, Drive entrance gate, Undated (Box 19)
      Sheet # 454
    - Detail of hinges for gates, Undated (Folder 22)
      Sheet # 455
      Format: Heavy paper - Card stock, likely
    - Planting plan, 1905 (Folder 22)
      Sheet # 456
    - Detail of architectural element, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 457
    - Sketch for garden, 1909 (Folder 22)
      Sheet # 458
    - Detail of Driveway gates, Undated (Box 19)
      Sheet # 459
    - Planting plan and key, Undated (Box 19)
      Sheet # 460
    - Arbor and lattice fence, by Architects Esenwein & Johnson, Undated (Folder 22)
      Sheet # 461
    - Planting plan, 1905 (Folder 22)
      Sheet # 462
    - Sketches and notes on gates, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 463
    - Second floor plan of cottage, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 464
    - South elevation of cottage, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 465
    - Details for cottage, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 466
    - East elevation of cottage, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 467
    - Suggestion for entrance treatment, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 468
    - Plan and section of reflecting pool, 1905 (Folder 22)
      Sheet # 469
  - Penton, John A. Location: Euclid, Ohio
    - Study of arrangement of grounds - Scheme C, 1906 (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2027
    - Study of arrangement of grounds - Scheme A, 1906 (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2028
    - Study of arrangement of grounds - Scheme D, 1906 (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2029
    - Study for service turn and stable entrance, Undated (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2030
    - # 113-3-A, Undated (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2031
    - Study of arrangement of grounds - Scheme B, 1906 (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2032
    - Survey of property, Undated (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2033
    - Plan of land, 1906 (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2034
  - Percy Warner Park Location: Nashville, Tennessee
    - Maintenance, 1928 (Folder 55)
      Sheet # 2045
      Note:2 copies
    - Scheme no. 1 - entrance park, 1928 (Folder 55)
      Sheet # 2046
    - Scheme no. 2, 1928 (Folder 55)
      Sheet # 2047
    - Scheme no. 3, 1928 (Folder 55)
      Sheet # 2048
  - Pierson, Mitchell Location: Pittsford, New York
    - Interiors - Bathroom #3, 1938 (Box 26)
      Sheet # 626
    - Plan and elevations - Bedroom # 1, 1938 (Box 26)
      Sheet # 627
    - Interiors - Bedroom #5, 1938 (Box 26)
      Sheet # 628
    - Servant's room # 2, 1938 (Box 26)
      Sheet # 629
    - Servant's room # 3, 1938 (Box 26)
      Sheet # 630
    - Servant's room # 1, 1938 (Box 26)
      Sheet # 631
    - Bedroom # 5 (owners), 1938 (Folder 24)
      Sheet # 632
    - Flooring pattern for hall, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 633
    - Interior - Flower room, 1938 (Box 26)
      Sheet # 634
    - Living room bay, 1938 (Box 26)
      Sheet # 635
    - Partial second floor hall plan, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 636
      Condition:Good, but half is missing
    - Study of second floor stair hall, 1938 (Folder 24)
      Sheet # 637
    - Study of north elevation of living room, 1938 (Box 26)
      Sheet # 639
    - Partial plan of hall, Undated (Box 26)
      Sheet # 640
    - Study of stairs, Undated (Box 26)
      Sheet # 641
    - Bedroom #2, 1938 (Folder 24)
      Sheet # 663
    - Second floor plan, 1938 (Folder 24)
      Sheet # 664
    - Living hall elevations, 1938 (Box 28)
      Sheet # 665
    - Details - Room 8, 1938 (Box 29)
      Sheet # 739
    - Room eight - plan and elevations, 1938 (Box 29)
      Sheet # 740
    - First floor hall details, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 741
    - Hall (First floor), 1938 (Box 29)
      Sheet # 742
    - Main entrance, 1938 (Box 29)
      Sheet # 743
    - Paneling plans, 1938 (Box 29)
      Sheet # 744
    - Attic door and paneling, 1938 (Box 29)
      Sheet # 745
    - Bedroom no. 4, 1938 (Box 29)
      Sheet # 746
    - Study of second floor stair hall, 1938 (Box 29)
      Sheet # 747
    - Owner's dressing room, 1938 (Box 29)
      Sheet # 748
    - Bathroom no. 1 and Dressing room, 1938 (Box 29)
      Sheet # 749
    - Bathroom no. 2, 1938 (Box 29)
      Sheet # 750
    - Breakfast room elevations, 1938 (Box 29)
      Sheet # 751
  - Plesset, Mrs. A. S. Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania
    - Rear elevation of Residence, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 853
    - Notes and Sketches on construction, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 854
      Format: Vellum, likely
    - Notes and Sketches on construction, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 855
    - Second floor plan, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 856
    - First floor plan, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 857
    - Second floor plan, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 858
    - Side elevation of residence, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 895
    - Side elevation of residence, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 896
    - Basement plan, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 897
    - Rough perspective sketch of house, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 898
    - Attic plan, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 899
    - Sketch plans for proposed residence, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 900
    - Sketch plans for proposed residence, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 901
    - Rough first floor plan, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 902
    - Sketch plans for proposed residence - Scheme "B", 1917 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 903
    - Front elevation of residence, Undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 904
  - Pound, Cuthbert W. Location: Unspecified
    - Planting about porch, Undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1538
  - Pratt, J. G. Location: Schenectady, New York
    - Study for arrangement of property (Box 73)
      Sheet # 2041
  - Proctor Park Location: Utica, New York
    - Description unspecified, 1911 (Mapcase-folder 51)
      Sheet # 1854
  - P. W. A. Housing Division Location: Lexington, Kentucky
    - Plot plan - Block A with architects: Associated Architects, 1936 (Folder 25)
      Sheet # 666
    - Plot plan - Block B with architects: Associated Architects, 1936 (Folder 25)
      Sheet # 667
    - Plot plan - Block C with architects: Associated Architects, 1936 (Folder 25)
      Sheet # 668
    - Plot plan - Block D with architects: Associated Architects, 1936 (Folder 25)
      Sheet # 669
    - Plot plan - Block E with architects: Associated Architects, 1936 (Folder 25)
      Sheet # 670
    - Plot plan - Block F with architects: Associated Architects, 1936 (Folder 25)
      Sheet # 671
    - Plot plan - Block G with architects: Associated Architects, 1936 (Folder 25)
      Sheet # 672
    - Plot plan - Block H with architects: Associated Architects, 1936 (Folder 25)
      Sheet # 673
    - Base bid block plan with architects: Associated Architects, 1936 (Folder 25)
      Sheet # 674
    - Landscape plan - Block E, Undated (Folder 26)
      Sheet # 675
      Format: Blueline
    - Landscape plan - Block G, Undated (Folder 26)
      Sheet # 676
    - Landscape plan - Block H, Undated (Folder 26)
      Sheet # 677
    - Landscape plan - Block D, Undated (Folder 26)
      Sheet # 678
    - Plant material types, Undated (Folder 26)
      Sheet # 679
    - Landscape plan - Block E, Undated (Folder 26)
      Sheet # 680
    - Block planting plan - Block C, 1936 (Folder 26)
      Sheet # 681
    - Block planting plan - Block E, 1936 (Folder 26)
      Sheet # 682
    - Block planting plan - Block F, 1936 (Folder 26)
      Sheet # 683
    - Block planting plan - Block G, 1936 (Folder 26)
      Sheet # 684
    - Block planting plan - Block H, 1936 (Folder 26)
      Sheet # 685
    - Plans of recreation areas, 1936 (Folder 27)
      Sheet # 686
    - Plans of recreation areas, 1936 (Folder 27)
      Sheet # 687
    - Base bid block plan, 1936 (Folder 27)
      Sheet # 688
    - Plant material types, 1936 (Folder 27)
      Sheet # 689
    - Block planting plan - Block A, 1936 (Folder 27)
      Sheet # 690
    - Plant material types, 1936 (Folder 27)
      Sheet # 691
    - Planting elevation studies, 1936 (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 692
    - Planting elevation studies, 1936 (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 693
    - Planting elevation studies, 1936 (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 694
    - Planting elevation studies, 1936 (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 695
    - Planting elevation studies, 1936 (Folder 28)
      Sheet # 696
    - Planting elevation studies, Undated (Box 34)
      Sheet # 932
    - Planting plan - Block "F", Undated (Folder 34)
      Sheet # 933
    - Planting plan - Block "C", Undated (Folder 34)
      Sheet # 934
    - Planting plan - Block "E", Undated (Folder 34)
      Sheet # 935
    - General landscape plan, 1936 (Folder 34)
      Sheet # 936
    - General landscape plan, 1936 (Folder 34)
      Sheet # 937
    - General landscape plan, 1936 (Folder 34)
      Sheet # 938
    - General landscape plan, 1936 (Folder 34)
      Sheet # 939
    - General landscape plan, 1936 (Folder 35)
      Sheet # 940
    - General landscape plan, 1936 (Folder 35)
      Sheet # 941
    - General landscape plan, 1936 (Folder 35)
      Sheet # 942
    - Plant material types, 1936 (Folder 35)
      Sheet # 943
- Series III. Clients R-Y
  - Ramsdell, H. T. Location: Buffalo, New York
    - Preliminary sketch, 1910 (Box 53)
      Sheet # 1597
    - Estimate of cost of landscape improvements, letter from Ramsdell, 1910 (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1616
  - Reis, Henry G. T. Location: Schenectady, New York
    - Property plan, 1908 (Box 52)
      Sheet # 1566
      Note:There is no sheet numbered 1565.
    - Study - Garden, Undated (Box 53)
      Sheet # 1586
    - Tracing of Wright sketch for entrance, 1909 (Box 76)
      Sheet # 1587
    - Plan showing arrangement about residence, 1908 (Box 76)
      Sheet # 1588
    - Map of lot, plan no. 171-1, Undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 1734
    - Map of lot, plan no. 171-2, Undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 1735
    - Sketch for staking, 1908 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 1736
    - Sketch for grading, 1908 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 1737
    - Front elevation, Undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 1738
      Note:Architect, Marcus J. Reynolds
    - Rear elevation, Undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 1739
    - West elevation, Undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 1740
    - East elevation, Undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 1741
    - Basement plan, Undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 1742
    - First floor plan, Undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 1743
    - Second floor plan, Undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 1744
    - Attic and roof floor plan, Undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 1745
    - Sketch plan of property, Undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
      Sheet # 1746
      Scale: 1"=2'
    - Plans for property, 1908 (Box 61)
      Sheet # 1758
  - Riordon Paper Company Limited Location: Junction of Ottawa and Rouge Rivers,(Prescott or Hawkesbury, Ontario, Canada)
    - Preliminary report on location of an industrial village - General Plan, 1910 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 524
      Scale: 1"=500'
    - Sketch of proposed tower and arcade, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 525
    - Sketch of proposed tower and arcade, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 526
    - Perspective of proposed industrial village, 1910 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 527
      Format: White lines on Brown - Reversed print (backwards)
    - Suggested types of architecture - elevations and plans, 1910 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 528
      Format: White lines on Brown - Backward print
    - Approximate survey sketch, 1910 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 529